Guide to the Emmons Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize, 3.75; (3 boxes)
  - OTHER OVERSIZE PAPERS
    - NAVAL SERVICE MATERIAL
      - Ship Journals and Letterbooks
        - George Foster Emmons
          - Letterbook of the U.S.S. Ossipee. Detached material: map of the Alaskan coast, 1867 (Box 33 (Broadside))
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 0.25; (1 box)
  Box 32, Restricted Fragile Papers, contains fragile originals. The material is arranged in folder order.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 7, folder 135 (Box 32, Folder 550)
  - Box 8, folder 141 (Box 32, Folder 551)
  - Box 9, folder 168 (Box 32, Folder 552)
  - Box 10, folder 180 (Box 32, Folder 553)
  - Box 11, folders 202, 210, 212 (Box 32, Folder 554)
  - Box 12, folder 215 (Box 32, Folder 555)
  - Box 13, folders 231, 237, 238 (Box 32, Folder 556)
  - Box 14, folders 250, 259-60 (Box 32, Folder 557)
  - Box 15, folders 278, 282, 286 (Box 32, Folder 558)
  - Box 16, folder 304 (Box 32, Folder 559)
  - Box 17, folders 317-323 (Box 32, Folder 560)
  - Box 19, folder 335 (Box 32, Folder 561)
  - Box 22, folder 390 (Box 32, Folder 562)
  - Box 23, folders 394, 401, 403, 407, 413, 415 (Box 32, Folder 563)